RG 074:068, Patricia M. Flowers Genealogical Papers, 1665-2006
Connecticut State Library
Patricia M. Flowers genealogical papers
1665-2006
Connecticut State Library
Flowers, Patricia M.
9 cubic feet
Contains notes, correspondence, photocopies of genealogical works, and miscellaneous genealogical research on the Flowers and Moulton families and related lines.
RG074_068
2011-010
Biographical Note
Patricia M. Flowers was born in New Hampton, New Hampshire on September 24, 1924, to Ralph Waldo Moulton and Mable Theodora Marsh Moulton. She married John F. Flowers on June 14, 1952 in Schenectady, New York.
Scope and Content
The collection is arranged into eight series:
Series 1. Flowers Family Files, 1848-2005, consists of notes and genealogical research.
Series 2. Flowers, Moulton Family Files, 1995, contains notes and genealogical research.
Series 3. Moulton Family Files, 1832-2004, includes notes, genealogical research, and photographs.
Series 4. Other Families Files, 1682-2005, consists of notes and genealogical research.
Series 5. Personal Papers, 1971-1997, contains correspondence.
Series 6. Publications, 1665-2000, consists of photocopies and published works.
Series 7. Subject Files, 1860-2002, consists of notes and photocopies.
Series 8. Reference, 1976-2006, consists of reference notes and materials.
Arrangement
Series 1. Flowers Family Files, 1848-2005
Series 2. Flowers, Moulton Family Files, 1995
Series 3. Moulton Family Files, 1832-2004
Series 4. Other Families Files, 1682-2005
Series 5. Personal Papers, 1971-1997
Series 6. Publications, 1665-2000
Series 7. Subject Files, 1860-2002
Series 8. Reference, 1976-2006
Index Terms
Subjects:
New Hampshire -- Genealogy; Ohio - Genealogy
Places:
Connecticut; New Hampshire; Ohio
Persons:
Flowers, John F., 1924-2007; Moulton, Patricia M., 1924-2014
Family Names:
Bishop family; Buell family; Carr family; Clark family; Clough family; Colby family; Flanders family; Flowers family; Friel family; Gibbons family; Gordon family; Hall family; Marsh family; McAwee family; Moulton family; Rush-Skinner family; Smith family; Sweeney family; Twombley family; Wolfe family
Document Types:
Correspondence; Genealogical tables; Genealogies; Photocopies; Photographs; Research notes
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
These papers were donated by Patricia M. Flowers to the Connecticut State Library on July 27, 2010.
Container List
- Series 1. Flowers Family Files, 1848-2005
  - Ancestors & Descendants of John F. Flowers, 1997 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
  - Ancestors & Descendants of John F. Flowers, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clark family, 2005 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Flowers, 1917-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Flowers ancestry, 1873-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12-17)
  - Flowers female lines, 1848-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18-23)
  - Flowers, miscellaneous, 1977-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Flowers, Palmer, Ferguson, 1976-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - John F. Flowers family, 1967-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - The Known Descendants of Hugh Friel and Eunice Gibbons, 1978 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Flowers, A-Z, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - References and sources, 1977-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5-9)
  - Descendants of Hugh Friel and Eunice Gibbons and Charles Sweeney and Mary McAwee, 1978-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10-14)
  - Flowers female lines: Rush-Skinner to Wolfe, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15-21)
- Series 2. Flowers, Moulton Family Files, 1995
  - Index to Ancestor Charts, Ancestor Charts, Lineages, 1995 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
  - Index to Ancestor Charts, Ancestor Charts, Lineages, 1995 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- Series 3. Moulton Family Files, 1832-2004
  - Bishop/Smith families, 1972-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Carr families, 1929-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5-10)
  - Clark family, 1915-2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Clough family, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Colby family, 1839-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14-16)
  - Gordon family, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Flanders family, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
  - Hall family, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 20-22)
  - Marsh ancestry, 1892-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - Marsh references, 1892-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - David K. Marsh, 1907-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Emeline Marsh, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Francenia June Marsh, 1925-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Frank Monroe Marsh, 1934-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - George Frank Marsh, 1891-1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - John Marsh, 1881-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Joseph Warren Marsh, 1870-1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ancestry of Mabel T. Marsh, 1903-2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chart of Mabel T. Marsh, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wilfred A. Marsh, 1917-1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts vital records, 1859-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Minnie's female lines, 1994-2003 (Box 4, Folder 19-22)
  - Miscellaneous family notes, 1906-1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Moulton ancestry, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1-10)
  - Moulton lineage, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Our Moulton Family, 1893-1991 (Box 5, Folder 12-14)
  - Patricia Moulton chart, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - New Haven vital records prior to 1901, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - References, 1832-1998 (Box 5, Folder 17-20)
  - Photographs, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Horace Elmer Twombly, 1883-1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lizzie A. Twombly, 1960-1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Series 4. Other Families, 1682-2005
  - Abbott to Allen, 1682-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Allerton to Bates, 1682-2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Batton to Brown, 1682-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Buell, 1682-2005 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Buffam to Byram, 1682-2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Carter to Cleverly, 1990-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Clough to Colton, 1990-2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Combe to Cushman, 1990-2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dagle to Dane, 1990-2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Day to Dowsett, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Drake to Dunbar, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dwight to Eddy, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Edson to Everett, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Farrington to Grantham, 1873-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Graves to Griswold, 1873-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gross to Gunne, 1873-2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Gurdon to Harvie, 1873-2003 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Haskins to Hoyt, 1880-2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Hubbard to Jewel, 1880-2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, 1880-2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - William Johnson, 1880-2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Jordan to Leach, 1880-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lee to Marche, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Marden to May/Mayes, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Meigs, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell to Ordway, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Osborne, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Osborne to Otis, 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Packard, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Padelford, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Paige to Parker, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Partridge to Porter, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Perkins, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Post, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pratt to Richardson, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Richmond, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ripley to Shaw, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Shayler to Stowell, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Straw, 1990-2004 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Street to Towner, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Towner, 1990-2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tracy to Whittemore, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wight to Wright, 1990-2004 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Lineages, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series 5. Personal Papers, 1971-1997
  - Christmas letters, 1971-1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Flowers and allied families, 1971-1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series 6. Publications, 1665-2000
  - American Catholics, 1959-1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Ancestry of Samuel Blanchard Ordway, 1844-1916, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut vital records, 1665-1867 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - First Ownership of Ohio Lands, 1910-1911 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - The Goddess of Duty and Honor: U.S.S. Nehenta Bay, undated (Box 8, Folder 14-17)
  - Life of General George Rogers Clark, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Marsh Family Bulletin, v. 1, no. 1-6, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - New Hampshire State Papers, Town Papers, Town Charters, 1902-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
  - Passengers of the Mary and John, 1630, 1987-1999 (Box 8, Folder 22-28)
  - Perry County, Ohio cemeteries, Coal and Salt Lick Townships, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Perry County, Ohio cemeteries, Pike Township, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Perry County, Ohio cemeteries, Redding Township, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Perry County, Ohio death records, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Perry County, Ohio obituaries, 1920-1924, report of deaths, 1882-1883, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Title pages, 1898-1902 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania vital records, v. I-III, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series 7. Subject Files, 1860-2002
  - Ohio references, 1938-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - DAR, 1971-1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Flowers/Friel families, 1973-2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Genie numbers, undated (Box 9, Folder 12-16)
  - Massachusetts county notes, 1883-1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts miscellaneous references, 1860-1882 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - New Hampshire county notes, 1824-1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New Hampshire miscellaneous references, 1853-1905 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Northend family, 1899-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NHDH, Concord, New Hampshire, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Ohio, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Rhode Island, 1871-1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sweeney family, 1877-2001 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - United States Census, Merrimack County, New Hampshire, 1860, 1880 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Series 8. Reference, 1976-2006
  - Books, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Cemeteries: gravestones - rubbings, 1976-1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Census, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Court: deeds and wills, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - D.A.R., 1993-2006 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Documentation, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Evidence - proof, 1977-1991 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Hereditary societies, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - German resources, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Government documents, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Immigration-naturalization, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Irish research, 1977-1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - LDS Family History Center, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Land records, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Libraries, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Library, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Loyalists, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Maps, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Massachusetts Archives, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Masters - charts and sheets, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Mayflower, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Medical - genetic, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Migrations, 1977-1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Military, 1980-1996 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - NEHGS - Boston, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Names, 1977-1993 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - National Archives, 1981-1999 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - National Genealogical Society, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Passenger lists & naturalization, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Pennsylvania research, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Photographs, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Printing, 1976-1993 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Problem solving, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Quakers, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Resources, 1977-1994 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Social Security, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Writing a book, 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 64)